okay so this here is kefir lime so we use it in our cocoa tea in making cocoa balls we use it at
christmas time in cake so just harvest it and just smell the aroma of this oh my gosh
come behind the seals with me to belmont estate in grenada as i try out
six new fruits that i've never had before i don't even know i realize now i've never seen a guava
like this we'll also learn some nutritional properties of the fruits and how you can use
them beyond just for eating there we go guava juice is my favorite guava juice and papaya
i'm passionate fruit is the king of fruits tell me why guava is the king of fruits
and also because it has a crown on it did you notice that yes it does have a crown on it
you need to break the skin a little bit so you can just even more yeah so here we make at belmont
we make ice cream with that and it's the most delicious even the leaves are fragrant so we use
that for making tea everything smells so aromatic like it's not muted at all oh my gosh this is
amazing i'm surprised bath and body works hasn't made a scent out of this
so it's like a passion fruit but very gentle very delicate so you just have to suck it out
you you um bite a hole up here right bite a hole big enough and then you squirt the entire
now big you need a hole open it up you gotta go go through all right okay now it's just squeeze
the entire thing in your mouth wow okay let me show y'all
so it's all these little seeds and then that is serious wow how did i never get this before
you described it perfect yeah it's but it's soft it's gentle water lemon so this is a mango lung
that's a mango lung you have to try it you take you take that home and it's good try it
and it's stringy yeah it is stringy let's see oh yes have you had water lemon no oh my gosh
okay let's see y'all mango lung it's gonna be in my teeth for the next two days
it's nice it's nice wow my favorite
that's nice i really don't want it in my teeth yeah well at least you got a taste i got a taste
said to work magical wonders this will keep you young quite a long period of time as well
fermented 15 20 days extract the juice so we consume in the juice
but the juice after fermentation does have a little smell may not be the best but it's
let's see
wow that's really terrible and but it is said to work a lot right because even in the common
cold your digestive system and all these things i know people who use it not to inside but on their
skin for pimples and stuff like that yeah acne breakout and stuff yeah yeah yeah listen well
beza is the nuni expert you know that's the right one let's listen beza's dad has been
doing products with nuni for a long time so beza has all the soup we make the juice the pulp
when you put it in the bowl it stay you sip all the juice then you put it in a cheesecloth you squeeze
you get a pulp and then they make the soup the leaf is good for pain as well just warm the bottom of the leaf
and you put it on the bowl and you put it on the bowl and you put it on the bowl and you put it on the bowl and the flower is for the ice
this is so weird looking isn't it good the bowl plant is an american plant it's an american plant
it's an american plant oh i was like i don't think so
this you don't have to throw this away put this to dry three four days after orange peel tea
it's very very good all of these leaves all the orange leaves the bergamot orange
there's a serious orange there that is it then what you think that is an orange
um you must leave making the cottage like it's right it's fried it up with oil onion and garlic
nice with bread sandwich you put it inside a sandwich
like a sandwich it's a different taste but the bird like the sandwich put it inside it
that doesn't even look like it's from this planet like it literally looks like other beings and then
there's a lot of species but uh if you see a tree that is covered with fruit it's so beautiful just
all these red fruits it's like a christmas tree yeah very very pretty ackee my first time this plant
it's like sweeter than sugar apple come right here very delicious right and it's like cocoa it grows
right of the stems and the backs of the tree right right right you can just bite into it and bite
into it and just yeah yeah sweet bite
bite hard just bite on a piece yo
you're good i love it you love it with all the acid
i expected you thought you were tricking me no because i love sour you thought you were tricking me
kelly kelly oh trick didn't work you like it you like tots i love it
okay okay sorry then i finally get your back so we call it condicea bilimbi and we also refer to it as
one finger you can put in like pepper sauces and stuff as well to give it a nice tiny flavor it also for
example you see the green bananas earlier when you're cooking green banana you can peel it right
but the stain gets in your hand get a few of these rub them in that green banana stain go on clean your
fingernails and all that as well i love that y'all thought you were going to trick me oh my god i thought
that one was going to send you off like yeah yeah yeah i love sour and listen i didn't tell kelly anything
you know i know the cat he planned something he knew where we headed i love sour this is beautiful
gotcha this setting right here is really beautiful with your colors the yellow and green and the yellow
green and the yellow and green and wrong do i like your lesson